your-story.org 2014-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Your Story

Your-Story.org is entirely owned by [24 Hour Trading Ltd](http://24hourtrading.co.uk/), a company registered in England and Wales.

Your privacy when accessing this, and any other website owned and operated by 24 Hour Trading Ltd is of paramount importance to us.

This Privacy Policy document explains what data we collect from web users, and how we use it.

### Information Gathered From Users

We collect two types of information from web users:

  1. Information you provide when signing up for _Your Story_ services, such as your name, email address, company bio and URL.
  2. Anonymised information is gathered in order to track page views and user interaction (such as visitor source, location, visit length and so on).

User information is collected in the following manners:

### Optional User Information

  1. **Press Release Submission** – we offer a number of Press Release submission services. Anything submitted through these methods may be published on the Your-Story.org website for web visitors, and may be available via internet search engines, third party website links and any other means not mentioned herein. Press releases will be published in perpetuity, unless you request deletion, or a Your-Story.org moderator decides to remove the press release from the website at his or her discretion at a later date.
  2. **Press Release Contacts** – when submitting press releases, users are requested to list public contact details within the body of the release. This information will be available publicly from the point of publication forwards.

### Children

We do not knowingly request personal and contact information from persons under the age of 13. Where it is apparent that a person under the age of 13 has submitted a press release or registered a Your-Story.org account, that account will be terminated immediately.

### Usage Tracking

We track user patterns throughout the Your-Story.org website. We do not correlate this information with data about individual users. We do break down usage based upon various datapoints provided by users’ browser and ISP, using Google Analytics tracking software.

For full information on the data that Google Analytics may collect, please see the following page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>

### Cookies

Google Anaytics software users Cookies to track your usage of Your-Story.org. Cookies are small files placed into the files your web browser store on your computer. They do not alter any settings, except storing small itmes of information such as times you accessed Your-Story.org. Data stored in these cookies contains no personal information about you. You may block cookies using your browser privacy settings – this will not impede your usage of Your-Story.org in any way.

### Third Party Advertisements

Your-Story.org derives revenue from the placement of third party advertisements within non-user submitted sections of the website. These advertisements are delivered by Google Adsense. You can read Google’s Privacy Policy here: <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>

### Security

Only Your-Story.org site administrators have access to private data submitted by users.

### Opt-Out Policy

You may opt out of submitting any data to Your-Story.org by taking the following steps:

  * Blocking Cookies on your browser;
  * Not accessing the Your-Story.org website in future;
  * Closing your Your-Story.org free account (all private data is removed absolutely; no record is kept);
  * Not registering a Your-Story.org free account.

### Payment Details

Certain services for Your-Story.org require you to make online payments. **We will not store your payment information**. We will pass on your payment information to a third party payment services provider, PayPal, who will execute the payment on our behalf. Payments should display on your credit or debit card statement as “24HRTRADING” or “PAYPAL*24HRTRADING” depending upon your payment choices.

### Your Consent

By accessing and using Your-Story.org, you are consenting to us using your data in the manner described above. In future, we may amend this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the operation of the website: please access this page frequently to keep abreast of the latest privacy policies adopted, and to ensure you are happy with the position.

At any time, you may contact us to close your Your-Story.org account, by emailing admin@your-story.org with your account username, registered email address and the words “delete my account” in the subject and body text of your message.
